Thanks for coming, girls. I want my best
friends to see the look on my dad's face
when he sees I'm not a failure. He even
said he would buy me an action figure if
I got a good grade on my Wonderbolts
flight test today.
>> Okie dokie. Can we go inside your cloud
house now? Even a small gust of wind
might be enough to blow me and my big
fat booty away. Haha.
>> Damn, this pink party pony is such a
tease. The [__] is just asking to get
farted on.
God damn. Nothing beats a stack of moon
pies and uh cold beer on a Wednesday
afternoon. Who knew all you had to do to
get free money was tax evasion?
There you are, [__] face. Go to the
fridge in the garage and fetch your pops
another cold one. Something tells me
this is going to be another long week of
hating my life.
>> Dude, Dad, I got something to show you.
>> Where is my beer? Christ. Dad, are you
still drunk? You got to lay off the
booze. My friends are over your
embarrassing me. This is why mom left
your [__] ass.
>> Don't lie around your friends to make me
look bad, you stupid [__] She's only
gone because she caught me cheating on
her. That's a totally different thing
than beer. God damn, I miss her so much.
That [__] had a pair of really big butt
cheeks that she could fart out of. That
was sexy.
So anyway, you promised you would buy me
a toy if I did well on my flight test
today.
>> I did? [__] I must have been drunk when
I said that.
>> Yeah, you did. And check it, dude. I got
a B+.
>> A B? That is so funny. I bet it stands
for [__] or beer. Damn, I could go for
a beer right now.
>> I was wondering if you could take me to
Toys R Us so you can buy me a really
cool Buzz Lightyear action figure that I
can show off to the Wonderbolts during
my next test. Toys R Us? You know we
ain't got money for that bougie crap.
Who even is this Buzz Lightyear chick
anyway? Is she a sexy Barbie or
something that I can shove up my ass?
>> He's a space ranger.
>> Space ranger? More like gay ranger. Let
me see what I have in my wallet.
>> Money.
>> Damn rainbow dash. I ain't got jack [__]
to bad to sad [__] But fear not, cuz
your daddy always thinks of something.
Here, go play with this instead and make
like a full ball sack and piss off.
>> A crushed up beer can.
>> That's not just any beer can. My little
dash. That's the one and only Bud
Lightyear, the brand new strictly
heterosexual superhero that just hit the
scene. Now, what do we say?
>> Yo, that's kind of awesome. Look how
flat it is. I I love it. Thanks, Pops.
>> Good. Now, take the car keys and pick me
up some more beer from the beer store.
>> Haha. Come on, every pony. Last one to
the car has to eat my ass.
>> Haha, Pinky, dear. I do believe prizes
are meant to be reserved for first
place. You know what? Maybe this Bud
Lightyear action figure is pretty cool
after all.
>> What's his superpower? He can turn evil
villains drunk and make them beat their
kids. He also pees himself when he can't
make it to a bathroom on time. Throw it
away. But it's my new toy.
>> A beer can isn't a toy, Rainbow Dash.
It's trash. You don't need to pretend to
be happy just because you didn't get the
toy you wanted.
>> Damn, Rainbow. Your family drives a
Bugatti.
>> Wrong card, [__] Ours is that
weirdass hell hippie VIN we got off
Craigslist for $13. Also, one of you
will have to drive because my license is
suspended. Later, Dell. God, I hate my
dad. I can see why mom left him for her
brother.
>> Don't you mean his brother?
>> No, all three of them are siblings. The
guy my mom is with now is my uncle named
Shitkitter. All of the names in my
family start with the word rainbow. Then
the second word has to do with movement.
I'm Rainbow Dash and my uncle is Rainbow
Shitkitter.
>> Hold up. Did you just say [__] skitter?
>> Yeah. What's wrong with it? Your name is
Twilight Sparkle.
>> Yeah, but my name isn't Twilight
Shitkitter.
>> Hey yo, Rainbow. What's your mama
called?
>> Rainbow Walking.
>> That's so basic.
>> Not any more basic than Rainbow Dash.
>> Okay, I got to ask. What is your dad's
name?
>> We just call him Dale.
>> D like the pickle.
>> No, just Dale, as in every Midwestern
dad's name.
>> Oh my god, Rainbow. You cannot be one of
those people who calls their adopted dad
by their real name.
>> Were you even listening to a goddamn
thing I said? Dell isn't his first name.
All of our names start with Rainbow. We
call him Dell because that's what he
wants to be called.
>> Well, what's his real name?
>> How the hell should I know?
>> So, are you two like dating?
>> No.
>> What would make you think something like
that?
>> I just noticed Pinkie Pie hasn't taken
her hand off your fat ass for 45
minutes.
>> Why don't you mind your own business
back there? Maybe she kind of has a
point, Pinkie Pie.
>> No, she doesn't. I just like the
vibrations of your ass on my hands when
we go over road bumps. Stop trying to
make it weird.
>> I don't think she has to try.
>> Hey, is that a Darren do action figure
on the dashboard?
>> Don't touch it. It goes up my ass.
Actually, don't touch anything in the
car. Pretty much all of it's been up my
ass. By the way, do you have any money
for the beer? I left my wallet back
home.
>> No,
>> you are no longer needed then.
Anyone else want to test my patience?
Hey, Twilight, how much money do you
have to give me for free?
>> I I think I may have a few quarters in
my butt crack.
>> [__] Well, wait, Ev, it'll be enough
for one can, I think. Dad will probably
yell at me, but I don't think I'll get
the belt this time. Stop the car, fat
ass, and go put the body in the trunk.
What have I done? Pinkie Pie,
Ponyville's most beloved party pony, is
dead. And it's all my fault. No. Rainbow
Dash is to blame for all this. Damn you,
Rainbow Dash.
Engine's dead.
>> Try it again.
>> I don't want to.
What do we do now? We're in the middle
of nowhere.
>> Don't worry. I was a Philly scout. I
know how to restart a car engine with
poop. Okay, while you [__] work on
getting the car fixed up, I'm going to
head on over to that gas station to get
some tasty cakes and energy drinks.
Out of the way, gorgeous. Mama needs her
cherry pies. Hot damn. Looks like the
moon didn't get the memo that the night
was done 6 hours ago.
Wait, that felt like mama, is that you?
Damn, [__] I haven't seen you since 8
months ago when you walked out on me.
You look old as [__] by the way. Hello,
Rainbow. How have you been?
>> Oh, you know, still living with dad, the
same dude you left me with. That's been
great. I'm just picking up beer. For
Dad,
>> I didn't leave you, Rainbow. I left your
father.
>> That is [__] You could have taken
me if you really wanted when you bounced
like a pair of balls.
>> It's not that simple. Doing that would
have pulled you out of the Wonderbolts
flight school. And I know how much being
a Wonderbolt means to you. No, I don't
like talking to people who make me mad.
Literally, the only thing that's good
about you is how fat your ass is. Each
butt cheek is like a really big
jellyfilled donut, except instead of
being filled with delicious jelly, it's
just full of poop. Father was right
about you after all.
>> God damn, I miss her so much. That [__]
had a pair of really big butt cheeks
that she could fart out of. That was
sexy.
Holy [__] more pies.
>> Hey, sugar baby. I saw what happened
with your mom just now.
>> What of it?
>> Well, you're acting like your mama left
when you were a poopy baby, but aren't
you like 27?
>> So what?
>> So you shouldn't hold it against your
mama because the only reason you're
still being abused by your daddy is
because of your own weakness and
unwillingness to walk away.
>> Why don't you shut the hell up? It's my
family affairs.
>> Yeah, you could just move out like your
mom did, but instead you would rather be
treated like a big poopy baby.
>> Excuse the hell out of you. I am not
being babyed.
>> You literally tried to impress your dad
just so he take you to Toys R Us.
>> That but dads are supposed to do that
for their kids.
>> But does he want to do that for you?
>> You two are right. And I know what
you're telling me to do.
>> That's good, Dash.
>> You're telling me to kill him. That is
not what we're saying.
>> Oh, hey, low IQ Beyblades. I wonder if I
should buy a couple for Pinkie Pie
because she's autistic.
>> Unbelievable.
What's up, sis? It's Starlight. She
needs me to pick up some Dr. Pepper.
>> Well, tell her no. We're buying carrots
so Twilight can put them in the ground
and act like she has a garden.
>> I have to go. If I don't, she hits me.
>> You don't have a spine with her. It's
like Starlight just snaps her hooves and
you come running. When was the last time
you told her no?
>> I'm not really sure, but it's fine. I
like doing things for her anyway.
>> That's exactly the problem. You want a
relationship with her, but a
relationship isn't one pony giving and
the other one taking. If you want to buy
her Dr. Pepper, you can use your own
cash. I'm out.
Uh, [__] Where is my Dr. Pepper? I
didn't get it.
Oh,
Marionette, what do you think you're
doing? What does it look like? I'm
carrying your purse for you. If you want
Dr. Pepper, you can get it yourself. I'm
going to the car.
You didn't get the Dr. Pepper.
>> No, you took my purse. You're being
really difficult on purpose. You know I
don't like it when you do that.
>> Are you going to drive or should I walk
back to the apartment?
>> I'm not going to have sex with you just
because you ask me to.
>> You're right. I'll just walk home.
>> No, it's 85° and you'll get heat stroke
under that mask.
Why are you making such a big deal about
this? It's just Dr. Pepper. It's the
principal, Marionette. You don't usually
say no. And when you do it, it's not
attractive. By the way, I want
hamburgers for dinner and you're going
to pay. I want pizza. Okay. So, now my
wants don't matter. They do, but so do
mine.
Hamburger pizza sounds good.
Pinky, stop pressing the trunk close
button. You so silly. We aren't going to
buy beer for my dad anymore. We're going
back to the house to kill him.
>> Wowee, that sounds super duper fun. Uh,
but worse Twilight and Rarity, we should
totally make this a girl's thing.
>> They went home, which is weird because I
thought they were our best gal pals. I
guess they don't want to be complicit in
my dad's murder or some [__]
>> Well, I'm going with you because loyalty
is real gangster [__]
>> Oh, yeah. I found this in the gas
station toy aisle, so I stole it. It
sort of made me think of you.
>> Oh, it it did. Why?
>> A you know, baby girl. because you're
autistic.
>> Uh, thanks,
>> Pinky. Why aren't you waving your hoofs
around all cutesy like you normally do
when you get excited? Aren't you
mentally challenged weirdo [__]
supposed to be proud when you're like
autistic and psychologically inadequate?
I don't get it. Like, I get being proud
of yourself, but why specifically proud
of being autistic when having autism
doesn't benefit you in any way? It's
like being born with one but cheek and
acting like that wouldn't suck some
major balls.
>> I am Dashy. I just don't really like how
you constantly buy me fidget toys and
boil me down to being the autistic
friend when I'm so much more than that.
How would you feel if I bought you beef
jerky all the time just because you're a
tomboy?
>> God, I would love that [__] Oh, come
on, Pinky. There's so much more to you
than autism.
>> Like what?
>> Your hair is big enough to hide things
in. And remember when you had the
courage to take a dump in the Ponyville
fountain the other day when you couldn't
make it to the bathroom on time and
almost got arrested? I think that's
pretty cool.
>> Where is your house?
>> Huh?
>> Like where is it?
>> I think it's that one right there.
>> Oh [__] Damn. I think that was my
neighbor. Actually, my dad is over on
that one.
Okay, let me try again. Sorry, Dashy. I
don't got another one in the tank. I had
a light lunch.
She's Fluttershy on her gay pink
scooter. Quick, pretend like we don't
hate her.
>> Hey girls, what are you doing all the
way out here?
>> Shut up.
>> Our car broke down and we need to get
back up to my house to kill my dad.
>> Why do you want to kill your dad?
>> It's a bit of a long story, but he owes
me a Buzz Lightyear action figure.
Well, I can fly up there and kill him
with you if you want. You would kill my
dad.
>> I will do it with you since we don't
hang out much and I am desperate for
companionship.
>> Don't you mean companionship?
>> I know what I said.
>> Hey, this is supposed to be mine and
Dash's adventure.
>> Sorry, Pinkie Pie. This is a Pegasus
job. It wouldn't be right of me to put
you in danger when I can risk
Fluttershy's life instead when no pony
cares about her.
Girls, you decided to help me after all?
>> No, sugar cube. We came to make sure you
didn't do something real damn stupid.
>> Hey, [__] Did you get the beer or do I
got to beat your ass?
>> No, I didn't get your beer.
>> Well, that's a shame. But I can't say
that I'm surprised because it's you. All
my life, you have done nothing but fail
me. Oh. Oh, well, you know the rules in
this house. Go wait in your room while I
go find a belt to beat you with on the
ass.
>> You know, Dad, I came back here to kill
you cuz you've been shitty to me my
whole life. But I won't because I have
friends on my side and killing you would
make me no different than you.
>> Can you hurry up and get to the point?
Because I honestly don't give a [__]
>> That was the point.
>> I don't really give a [__]
I'm helping.
>> Pinkie Pie, you [__] I changed my
mind. I wasn't going to do it anymore.
>> But But I'm helping.
>> No, you're not. You just killed my dad
in cold blood.
>> He didn't care about you, Rainbow Dash.
But I do, so I don't regret protecting
you.
>> Where the hell do you think you're
going, Pink [__] This isn't just
something you can walk away from. I'm
going to go to Toys R Us to buy you the
toy you wanted. Your dad said he'd get
you a toy if you did good. He didn't, so
I will.
>> Pinky, a toy can't fix this. You can't
replace him.
>> I'm not trying to replace anyone,
Twilight. I'm I'm just helping my
friend.
>> If you want to help me, how's about
letting me have a go with that ass?
Dear Princess Celestia,
Pinkie Pie killed some pony today.
Dear Princess Celestia, today something
happened.
Dear Princess Celestia,
Princess Celestia, you're already here.
Did you read my mind all the way from
Canterlot?
>> No, my little pony. I've just been here
in your garden eating your carrots
because I am a horse. I already know
what happened with Pinkie Pie, but rest
assured that she will not be punished.
>> But I don't understand. She killed
someone.
>> Rainbow Dash's father had 1,832
active warrants.
>> But that doesn't make it right.
>> That is something we can agree on. All
ponies should be friends. But I'm afraid
the real world is not as gentle as the
lessons we are taught my young student.
Unfortunately, there are times where for
horses, the only option left is to
viciously draw blood from our enemies.
And Pinkie Pie felt today was one of
those days. Oh, yeah. And there's also
this.
>> A Buzz Lightyear toy. Why do you have
this?
>> I stole it from Rainbow Dash's front
porch.
>> Pinky got it after all. That's sweet of
her, I guess.
No, Twilight, that came from Rainbow
Dash's father.
>> That doesn't make sense.
>> He ordered it with Door Dash from
Walmart after his daughter, Rainbow
Dash, left to buy him beer. He intended
it to be a surprise for her.
>> But why?
>> Because very few ponies are purely good
or purely awful. And you of all ponies
should understand that. And because of
Pinkie Pie, Rainbow Dash may never get
the chance to realize that herself.
Pinkie Pie, stop throwing fidget
spinners at my window before I unal
alive you. Did you ever know that you're
>> girl? What the hell are you doing out
there?
>> What? What are you saying? I can't hear
you.
>> Don't throw [__] at my house.
I want you to know I know the truth. Of
course I know it. I would be without
you.
Did you ever know that you're
>> Pinkie Pie? Spitfire. What are you
[__] doing here? Spitfire wanted to
give you something dashy.
>> You mean I'm in the Wonderbolts?
>> Well, not actually. See, since you got a
B instead of an A, your Wonderbolt
uniform will be brown and yellow like
[__] and piss instead of the normal cool
blue and yellow version we wear because
you failed so everyone will know you
weren't good enough. It's kind of a
punishment thing for loser [__] but
you can just retry later if you want to
get a normal blue and yellow one and be
a real Wonderbolt.
>> Are you kidding, [__] I prefer this
one because when everyone looks at me
perform with the Wonderbolts, they'll
know I'm the [__]
>> Yeah, Dashy, you're the real winner in
my eyes. Since your Wonderbolts costume
is brown and yellow, you can pee
yourself and also poopy and no pony will
notice.
I hope you like me.
If you do, I like you, too.
Why don't you try me?
I'm lost when I'm with you.
I don't know if you share this light.
Think about you late at night.
I'm wondering if this feeling
is
true.
I hope we're more than just friends.
I hope you feel this, too.
I hope I'm more than just friends.
I want to be with you.
What if you say no?
But what if you say yes I do?
Tired of laying low. I'm lost when I'm
with you.
I don't know if you shed this light.
Think about you late at night.
I'm wondering if this feeling
is
true.
I hope I'm more than just friends.
I hope you feel this, too.
I want to be with you.
I hope I'm more than just friends.
I hope you feel this, too.
I hope we're more than just friends.
I want to be with you.
I want your friends.
I feel
I want to be with you.